Abdulaziz Albadawi

Full-Stack Designer

Abdulaziz Hamad Albadawi

Cairo, Egypt

(+20) 127 121 8832 albadawiabdulaziz@gmail.com

Skills

I have experience with more than 3 years in UI/UX design, I have mastered Adobe Illustrator and Photoshop, Figma, Adobe XD, InVision and Adobe InDesign, I have studied the design fundamentals and theories by courses from Adobe, Udemy and TheFutur Academy.

Experience

Quak ~ Lead Designer

October 2018- September 2019, Cairo, Egypt

I led the research, prototyping, usability testing, and design the new version Beta 1.0.0.

I also helped design the MVP Quak.

Freelancer ~ Full-stack designer

January 2017 - October 2018, Giza, Egypt

I designed logos, websites, posters, user interfaces and various social media content for multiple clients. The majority of this work was completed remotely.

Rubium studio ~ Product Designer

July 2019- PRESENT, Cario, Egypt

I contact with the client and deal with them and do the research, wireframing, creating the website interfaces then I test it with the art director

Education

El- Neel School/ Computer Science

October 2014- EXPECT OCTOBER 2019, Cairo, Egypt

Studied Computer Science, I chose Data analysis career and got the first place in my school, I learnt powerful software like Python, SQL, Spreadsheet, Machine Learning etc.

Awards

Best learner and most productive learner for 5 weeks in row ~ DataCamp The perfect student Award ~ Regional Government Best speech ~ Cairo International Model United Nation 1st place for my research on how to achieve goal ~ El-Neel School